市川!
Ichikawa!
什么?
What?
比目鱼不是晩上才出来吗
Don't flatfish come out at night?
有些也会在白天游到岸边
Some swim up to shore in daytime.
大的那种
Big ones.
试试看 泡菜汤 一炖好吃的很
Try them, bro. They're great for kimchi stew.
有一次我在餐车上吃过
I tried it in a diner.
你还是不明白
You really don't get it.
餐车上能给你吃好的比目鱼吗
They don't serve the good ones at some lousy diner.
你肯定吃的是假货
You ate that fake stuff.
假货的是什么意思?
What do you mean fake?
我没有冒犯您的意思
I didn't mean to offend.
你鱼饵是不是有问题?
Something wrong with your bait?
有可能
Could be.
也许我可以拿你小姆指当饵
Maybe I should use your pinky.
你可别惹我
Don't fuck with me!
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
对不起
Sorry!
有人忘在办公室了我就拿来了
Someone left it in the office, so I took it.
别带到这儿来 蠢货!
Don't bring it here, dumb-ass.
对不起
Sorry.
太他妈 危险了!
Damned dangerous!
臭婊子!
Bitch!
臭婊子?
Bitch?
你这个荡妇 !
You slut!
你个臭不要脸的!
Whore!
转过身
Turn around.
这是什么?
What are these?
你还有钱混蛋
You have money, asshole.
下一个该你了
You're next, Yoo Hee.
生意不太好是吧
Business is slow, huh?
他在抱怨我们的姑娘
He's complaining about our girls.
过来一趟
Come over.
好 马上就来
Okay, in a second.
有个日本黑社会的在投诉 要见老板
A Japanese yakuza is complaining. He's asking for the boss.
黑社会的? -是的
Yakuza? Yes.
在哪儿? -太阳度假酒店
Where? Taehang Resort Hotel.
这边请
This way.
你们两个没用的臭婊子
You useless bitches!
老板要拿我撒气了
He'll take it out on me.
你们没事吧?
You alright?
他提出变态的要求 我们不同意他就打我们
He wanted sick stuff. We said no, so he hit us.
有什么问题?
What's the problem?
你们这两个婊子哭丧个脸
Your bitches are pathetic.
我老板很生气
Our boss is angry.
他说了不会付钱的
He says he won't pay.
你老板在哪儿?
Where's your boss?
在卧室
In the bedroom.
你对我们姑娘有什么问题?
What's your problem with our girls?
我有问题?你个傻帽
My problem? You idiot.
你们这些鸡太差劲了
Your bitches are lame.
得好好培训! 一点情趣都不懂
They need training! They're no fun at all.
看起来你很有情趣
Looks like you had fun.
别在这跟我扯皮l
Don't fuck with me!
我可不是在跟你扯皮!
I'm not fucking with you!
你弄伤了我们的姑娘 我们要求赔偿
I'm demanding compensation for hurting our girls.
你知道我是谁吗?
You know who I am?
我是花菱组的花田
I'm Hanada of the Hanabishi family.
你这是要跟花菱组作对吗?
You want trouble with the Hanabishi?
听着…
Listen...
我还有个结拜的兄弟在首尔
I even got a sworn brother in Seoul.
混蛋!
Asshole!
你现在不是在首尔 这里是济州岛
You're not in Seoul. This is Jeju Island.
别跟我吹什么花菱组的屁话了
Drop the Hanabishi crap.
有胆子就来吧!
Bring it on!
别激动
Relax.
我来是玩的
I just came to have some fun.
没必要吵
No need to quarrel.
是你挑起来的
You're the one asking for it.
你想怎么解决 蠢货?
How will you settle up, asshole?
我身上没带现金
I don't have cash on me right now.
你明天中午过来
You can come tomorrow at noon.
你能付多少钱?
How much can you pay?
两百万
Two million.
你不是说的韩元吧
You can't mean Korean won.
不是要两百万日元吧!那也太高谱了!
Not two million yen! That's outrageous!
你看…
Look...
想想你之前干的事情再说
Think about what you did before blurting out a sum.
我能把你脸剁碎了喂鱼
I'll mince your face and use it as bait!
好的 好的
Okay, Okay.
给你两百万日元
You'll get your Japanese yen.
本字幕首发于字幕库 www.zimuku.cn
额…你叫什么名字老弟?
Say... What's your name, buddy?
你是日本人?
You Japanese?
我名字叫滚开
My name is Fuck Off.
听到了吗 ?
Got that?
钱一次付清!
Pay up!
给那个人
To that guy.
嗨
Hey.
没用的保標!
Useless bodyguards!
对不起
Sorry.
他们刚才那样羞辱我 你们两个在干嘛?
They humiliated me. And you two?
你们眼睁睁站在那里看着
You stood there and watched!
对不起先生
Sorry, sir.
我明天早上离开
I'm leaving in the morning.
事情你们处理 -钱从哪儿来?
Take care of this. With what money?
蠢货!
Dumbass!
我们不会给那些杂种付钱的
We won't pay that bastard.
要是他敢找茬
If he makes a fuss,
就干掉他
kill him!
是的先生
Yes, sir.
中田…
Nakata...
花田在哪儿?
Where's Hanada?
他迟到了?
Is he late?
西野若头
Underboss Nishino,
他在韩国处理紧急事务
he's in Korea on urgent business.
例会他肯定回来参加
He's due back for the regular meeting.
什么事务
Business?
他的正经事就是坐这儿来开会!
His business is to get his butt here!
我跟他说过了他说机会难得
I told him. He said the offer was too good.
这是他留给野村组长的
He left this for Chairman Nomura.
别想越过我去拍野村先生的马屁
Don't go over my head to gain Mr. Nomura's favors.
这种事你必须先向我汇报
You must report first to me on these matters.
我道歉
My apologies.
我们没有这个意思
That's not what we meant.
算了吧
Forget it.
我以后会跟他解释的
I'll explain it to him later.
谢谢
I appreciate it.
下午好先生
Good afternoon, sir.
野村怎么回事?
What's with Mr. Nomura?
怎么总是要跟人会谈?
And his constant meetings?
这个月都几次了?
How many this month?
他是个生意人 没有会谈不自在
He was a trader. He's uncomfortable without meetings.
为什么他是接班人?
Why should he be successor?
就算他是前任组长的女婿又怎么样!
So what if he's the ex-boss' son-in-law!
说什么只有会花钱才能赚到更多的钱
He says spending is the only way to make more money.
他给我们带来了巨大的损失
He's causing huge losses!
兄弟你说话声音太大了
Brother, you're talking too loud.
我才不在乎呢
I don't give a shit.
我不会允许那家伙胡来的
I won't allow what's-his-name
好像这是他的地盘一样
to act like he owns this place!
还有件事中田
One more thing, Nakata.
你每个月都从花田那边拿到不少的钱
You receive a lot of money from Hanada every month,
是不是这样?
isn't that right?
没有我一分也没拿到
No, I'm not getting any.
要不是你把他介绍给野村
Without your recommendation to Mr. Nomura,
花田根本不可能有自己的组
Hanada would never have his own family.
他就不会毛遂自荐过去吗 ?
Couldn't he have appealed to him in person?
靠钱吗?
With money?
他的生意发展的很快
His business is thriving.
高利贷 贩毒 只要赚钱他什么都干
Loansharking to meth dealing, he does whatever makes money.
暴徒不行了他就招了一帮摩托党
He recruits biker gangs to avoid mob busts.
警局他也有路子
He uses police connections at his convenience.
他干的很不错
He's quite impressive.
他从韩国弄的毒是吗?
He gets the meth in Korea, right?
前组长禁止他搞毒品
The ex-boss prohibited meth.
野村呢?
And Mr. Nomura?
他不干涉…
He wouldn't interfere...
只要价格合适!
if the price was right!
是的
Yeah.
抱歉
Excuse me.
人都到了
Everyone's here.
很好
Fine.
都坐下吧
Remain seated.
这个月有些什么事情?
Anything happen this month?
没什么特别的
Nothing unusual.
Sawamura will remain hospitalized for another couple months.
我们有个叫河野的干部
We have an executive named Kono...
他这个月出狱
He'll be released from prison soon.
很好我希望每个组准备一份现金恭贺一下
Fine. I expect each family to prepare a cash gift.
干部出狱都得大方点
An exec's release calls for significant contributions.
别太小气搞得自己很难看
Don't embarrass yourselves.
是的先生
Yes, sir.
你觉得你是个了不起的黑社会 ?
You think you're big yakuza?
光会吹牛是不会来钱的
Bragging won't boost your income.
是谁跟警察和政府的人打交道
Who dealt with the Security Police
重建了这个组?
and the government to rebuild this family?
中田花田在哪儿?
Nakata, where's Hanada?
我跟若头说了 他在韩国处理紧急事务
As I told Underboss, he's in Korea on urgent business.
他知道我要来还外出?
He travelled, knowing I was here?
例会上你们都要向我汇报我是你们的组长
You all report to me, your Chairman, at these regular meetings!
是
Yes.
要是前组长在他肯定不会外出的
He surely would have been here for the former boss.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
就是我说的意思
I mean exactly what I said.
西野你可别惹我
Don't fuck with me, Nishino.
你那帮人花钱像流水赚钱屁本事没有
Your lot spends money like water and knows nothing about making it.
我为这个组呕心沥血
I sweat blood for this family!
动动你的猪脑子!
Use your fucking brain!
那个傲慢的西野一有机会就藐视我
That arrogant Nishino defies me every chance he gets.
他是叫人头疼
He can be a pain in the ass.
有没有可能降了他的级 ?
Any possibility to demote him?
可以让中田或者花田替换掉西野
Nishino could be replaced by Nakata or Hanada.
不过西野那帮手下不会坐视不管的
But Nishino's loyal supporters won't take it lying down.
那么我们就选中田做新会长
Then we choose Nakata as a new boss.
让他去和西野斗
Let him fight Nishino.
这样我们一石二鸟
We'll get rid of two old farts with one blow.
大哥
Brother,
就这么算了吗?
won't you do anything?
他特妈的死了
He's fucking dead.
你要怎么办?
What will you do?
我正在考虑 蠢货!
I'm busy thinking, dumb-ass!
这怎么回事?
What's that about?
韩国明星吗?
Some Korean star?
对不起我刚染了头发
Sorry. I just dyed my hair.
有个日本黑道的人找在 我们死了个兄弟
There was trouble with a Japanese yakuza. We lost a man.
大友先生想要报仇
Mr. Otomo wants to return.
你们自己想办法解决别动粗
Work it out amongst yourselves. Solve it peacefully.
告诉大友别给我们惹麻烦
Tell Otomo to spare us any trouble.
是
Yes.
我们一个若众用冰镐把那家伙据死了
Our soldiers stabbed the guy to death with an ice pick.
尸体扔到沙滩上了
They dumped him on the beach.
扔了?要是引起帮派斗争怎么办?
Dumped? What if this turns into war?
是啊
Yeah.
我不知道济州岛还有黑社会
I don't know any yakuza in Jeju.
嗨 老枪
Hey, Gun.
什么?
Yes?
丸山!
Maruyama!
你他妈在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
我在吃院文考
I'm eating barbecue.
你是不是傻?我跟你说了在外面等着!
Are you stupid? I told you to wait outside!
对不起先生
Sorry, sir.
我招他来参加摩托党的
I recruited him from a biker gang.
谁知这家伙是个蠢蛋
But he's a butthead.
给您的 酒馆送您的
For you, compliments of the house.
非常感谢
Thanks a lot as always.
不用谢我们欠您太多先生
You're welcome. We owe you so much, sir.
请随时光临我们的酒吧 白天都营业的
Please drop by our bar. It's open during the day.
恩你不是从济州岛来的吗 ?
Say, aren't you from Jeju Island?
是的
Yes.
济州岛的酒店和赌场谁操控的 ?
Who controls the hotels and casinos in Jeju?
那是张组长的地盘
That's the turf of Chairman Chang.
他有个拜把子兄弟尹也在那一带混
His sworn brother Yoon is also there.
张组长?
Chairman Chang?
东京的?
Of Tokyo?
是的 最开始他是从济州岛出去的
Yes. He's originally from Jeju.
那边出什么事了?
Something happen there?
没什么你可以走了
Nothing. You're excused.
该死
Dammit.
你麻烦大了
You messed up.
你惹错人了
You picked the wrong fight.
张组长在日本和韩国都是个有影响的人物
Chang is an influential figure in both Japan and Korea.
你在酒店吵架的那个…
Your argument in the hotel...
那人是不是叫大友?
Was the guy named Otomo?
我…我真的不知道
Well... I really don't know.
他杀了那个叫片岗的条子
He killed that cop Kataoka.
据说就在葬礼举办现场旁边
Right by the funeral site, they say.
我想肯定是张组长罩着他
I think Chang gave him shelter.
那你觉得我该怎么办?
So what do you think I should do?
话要是传到野村或是西野那儿
Say one word to cross Nomura and Nishino,
你就死定了
you'll be dead.
听着
Listen.
我要去东京张组长的办公室拜访一下
I'll go to Tokyo and visit Chang's office
向他道歉
to apologize.
给我准备点钱
Prepare some money.
准备多少?
How much should I prepare?
两千万到三千万日元
20 to 30 million yen, as condolences.
你杀了那个家伙
You did kill a guy.
这么多?
That much?
傻叉!
Idiot!
张已经那么有钱了
Chang's got shitloads of money.
有礼貌一点
Respond in a sincere manner,
他会明白的
he'll understand.
对他们来说不过是少了个讨厌的废物 - 是的
All they lost is one lousy punk. Yeah.
是花菱组?发生什么事了?
The Hanabishi? Is something going on?
有点事
Kind of.
中田和花田正在商量…
Nakata and Hanada are talking...
要去找张先生道歉
about apologizing to Mr. Chang.
真的?谢谢你的消息 老枪
Really? Thanks for the tip, Gun.
尹夫人还好吗?
Is Mrs. Yoon alright?
她两天前去世了
She passed away two days ago.
我去葬礼上献花
I sent flowers for the funeral.
看到…
I see...
只有那些和尹先生关系近的人被通知了
Only those close to Mr. Yoon were contacted.
这消息我会告诉张先生的
I'll inform Mr. Chang.
好的
Fine.
李先生?
Mr. Lee?
怎么了?
What?
花菱组的人准备过来跟我们道歉
The Hanabishi will visit us to apologize.
我们怎么办?
What do we do?
看看他们打算怎么做吧
It depends on what they offer.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
这是老枪 还的债务利息
This is from Gun. Interest on a debt.
告诉他我不需要这个
Tell him I don't need it.
伙计们我准备走了
Guys, I'm leaving.
好的先生
Yes, sir.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
张先生安排好了一切
Mr. Chang arranged everything.
官方说是死于意外
It's officially death by accident.
反正钱能解决一切
Money solves everything.
市川…- 嗯?
Ichikawa... Yes?
光野死了 你还在这钓鱼?
Ko is dead. How can you fish?
我钓鱼也不是在找乐子
I'm not having much fun.
我准备去日本杀了那个混蛋!
I want to run to Japan, and kill that motherfucker!
你以为只有你很生气吗?
You think you're angry?
我也一样!
I feel the same!
我们走吧
Let's go.
好
Yeah.
给老板当司机太不容易了
It sucks being a chauffeur for the head family.
当然
Sure does.
你不能这么说笨蛋!
You can't say that, dickhead!
从大阪远道而来幸苦了
Thanks for coming all the way from Osaka.
我们坐新干线先到东京
We took the Shinkansen Express to Tokyo.
是吗?
Really?
哪位是花田?
So who's Hanada?
我是花菱组的花田
I'm Hanada of the Hanabishi.
花菱组…他妈的什么东西?
Hanabishi... So fucking what?
如果他们有敬意就应该野村或西野来啊
Nomura or Nishino should be here, if they had any respect for the code!
若头輔佐?这个头術是个安慰奖吗?
Deputy Underboss? Is that a consolation prize?
野村先生刚接任了这个位置
Mr. Nomura just took over the post.
有一堆麻烦事等着西野先生解决
Mr. Nishino has screw-ups to resolve.
你是指这件事不麻烦吗?
You saying this isn't a screw-up?
我没那个意思
I didn't mean that at all.
你他妈的到底什么意思?
What the hell did you mean?
一个真正的日本黑道人会为此砍下一根手指
A real Japanese yakuza would chop off a finger.
你这点钱只够喂鸡的
This money's just chicken feed.
它解决不了什么事
It won't settle everything!
我们可以出去打一场
We could go to war.
不必生气 伙计们
No need to get angry, fellows.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你去安抚过
Did you take good care
光野家属了吗?
of Ko's bereaved family?
还没 抱歉 我现在就去
Not yet, sorry. I'll do that now.
下午好
Good afternoon.
先生
Sir,
这是中田先生和花田先生
Mr. Nakata and Mr. Hanada
来自大阪的花菱组
of the Hanabishi in Osaka.
我们的人在你的地盘上做错了事
Our man seems to have misbehaved on your turf.
我们对此真的很抱歉
We're truly sorry about it.
请原涼他
Please forgive him with this.
这是干嘛?
What's this for?
为光野的死来道歉
An apology for Ko Seong-Jin's death.
带着这三千万的现金
With this measly 30 million cash,
他们来请求我们的原谅
they ask for our forgiveness.
你再去拿三千万来
Bring another 30 million cash.
什么?
What?
去拿钱
Just get the money.
那些杂种根本没有尊重
Those bastards have no respect.
好
Alright.
他用韩语在说什么? 一点不尊重我们
What is he babbling in Korean? They're disrespecting us.
把钱给他们然后我们就走
Give them the money and split.
当时是你让我在野村和西野没发现之前行动的啊
You're the one who told me to act before Nomura or Nishino found out.
他们在跟我们捣蛋 笨蛋
They're messing with us, stupid.
我们都给三千万了 为什么还让他们羞辱我们?
Why let them humiliate us when we are paying 30 million?
不过死了个人 五百万就够了
5 million is really enough for a fucking soldier.
你!
You!
你刚在说什么?
What did you say?
我们一个人的性命就值五百万吗?
My precious man's life is worth only 5 million?
你们的态度直接影响了这件事能否解决
Your attitude determines if we're your poison or your antidote.
出去!
Get out!
都给你们
All yours.
什么?
What?
滚!
Go!
我猜张能听懂日语
I guess Chang understands Japanese.
这他妈的不是重点
That's not the damn point.
我们怎么处理这些钱?变成六千万了
What do we do with the money? It's doubled to 60 million.
他们给新组长准备的贺礼?
Congratulatory cash gift for the new chairman?
你真是个笨蛋
You're such a stupid ass.
他们这是逼着花菱组内斗
They are pushing the Hanabishi to fight.
给野村和西野各1亿然后砍掉你的手指
Pay 100 million each to Nomura and Nishino, and cut your finger.
真要那样? -什么真要那样?
Really that much? "Really that much"?
这些年你挣了多少钱?
How much did you earn in the last couple years?
靠毒品和高利贷差不多赚了几十亿
A couple billion by meth dealing and loan-sharking alone.
我们没有选择!
We have no fucking choice!
兄弟求你帮忙解决这件事
Brother, I beg you to resolve this.
你要知道这不便宜
It won't be cheap though.
我明白了
I got that.
你说你们背着我们
You're saying you went behind our backs
去找了张
to visit Chang.
抱歉
Sorry.
张不仅没收我们的钱
Chang didn't only refuse our money.
他给我们又拿了三千万回来
He gave us an additional 30 million.
你到底有多蠢?
How stupid are you?
他的意思是
His message was:
至少带六千万来
Bring at least 60 million.
傻子
Idiots.
花田
Hanada.
是的先生
Yes, sir.
你不仅对
You didn't only lie
野村先生和我撒谎
to Mr. Nomura and I...
你还去韩国找乐子
You went to Korea for pleasure.
真会享受啊
What luxury!
不是这样
Not really.
我完成了自己的工作
I completed my work
在去济州島之前
before stopping briefly on Jeju Island.
我们在四处为野村先生奔波
While we were rushing around for Mr. Nomura,
而你在济州島玩女人
you were buying women in Jeju.
现在你想我们给你
Now you want us to clean up
擦屁股?
your shitty mess?
抱歉
Sorry.
我不是故意给你惹麻烦的 野村先生
I didn't mean to cause trouble for you, nor Mr. Nomura.
问题是你脑子里有病!
The trouble is you have shit for brains!
白痴!
Moron!
算了吧
Forget it.
我会去说服张解决问题的
I'll convince Chang and settle things.
花田
Hanada,
你跟我来
you come with me.
好
Yes.
野村先生非常忙
Mr. Nomura is a very busy man.
组长!
Mr. Chairman!
我去找张来解决这个事
I'll go over to Chang's office and settle this.
花田…
Hanada...
跟我来
Come with me.
若头?我能去吗?
Underboss? May I?
你留下打理野村先生的公司
You keep Mr. Nomura company.
西野可以和张密谋
Nishino could secretly conspire with Chang
从花田那里搞点钱
to mooch money off Hanada.
他想从花田那搞点东西
He wants to squeeze Hanada.
如果西野露面了应该能说服张
Chang will be convinced of that if Mr. Nishino shows up.
但是西野总出现在很多重要场合
But Nishino shows up for all important occasions.
很难看出老板到底是谁
It's hard to see who the boss is.
对吗?
Right?
没错l
For sure!
他是为野村先生和花菱组而工作
He works hard for Mr. Nomura and the Hanabishi.
你和他待在一起的时候没觉察到吗?
Haven't you noticed while you're with him?
你跟他们一伙的?
Are you one of them?
什么?
What?
他讨厌野村先生当了组长成了他的老板
He hates that Mr. Nomura became chairman ahead of him.
难道他不想等野村先生退休接任组长吗?
Doesn't he want Mr. Nomura to retire so he can take over the role?
他不想这样
He doesn't think like that.
你跟西野想法一样吗?
Do you agree with Nishino?
你不想我当组长?
You hate that I became chairman?
因为我之前不过是个做股票交易的?
Because I was a stock trader?
你认为花菱组跟着我没有发展口号?
You think the Hanabishi haven't flourished with me?
我还没选西野作为我的接班人
I have not chosen Nishino as my successor.
你当初对我对花菱组的承诺
Your commitment to me, to the Hanabishi...
那是决定因素
that's the determining factor.
明白了吗?
Is that clear?
那你怎么想呢?
So what do you think?
关于什么?
About what?
我问你是否愿意接替我的职位
I'm asking if you are willing to take over my role.
我不能位居兄弟之上
Not ahead of a brother.
你没看见吗?
Don't you see?
你还能忠心多久?
How much longer can you be so loyal?
如果西野成为组长 你就是他最大的眼中钉
You would be his biggest obstacle if he becomes chairman.
他能毁了你的家庭赶走花田
He would crush your family, drag Hanada out,
吞了我的财产
and go after my assets.
不
No.
听着 中田
Listen, Nakata.
我希望你能接替我这个花菱组长的位置
I want you to succeed me as chairman of the Hanabishi.
正如你们再背后议论我的 我不是从底层摸爬滚打上来的黑道人
As you say behind my back, I'm not an up-from-the-ranks yakuza.
我知道什么时候该退出
I know when to quit.
好好想想
Think it over.
你们同意吗?
You guys agree?
他真的是在为你的将来考虑
He is very considerate to think ahead for you.
我们完全同意他兄弟
We totally agree with him, brother.
花田
Hanada,
本字幕首发于字幕库 www.zimuku.cn
再准备个2亿
prepare another 200 million.
各拿1个亿
100 million each
给我和张
for Chang and myself.
我已经准备好了两份1亿现金
I already ordered 100 million each to be delivered
给野村和你
to Mr. Nomura and yourself.
花田 听着
Hanada, listen...
你随时可以拿回你的钱
You can get your money back anytime you want.
总有一天
One day,
当我掌管花菱组的时候
when I rule the Hanabishi family,
我会选你做我的若头
I would handpick you to be my underboss.
一切都会好起来
Then everything will be mighty fine.
你说真的?
Are you sure?
真的
I'm sure.
明天早上第一件事就是去找张
Let's go to Chang's office first thing tomorrow morning.
和我一起去事情很快就能解决
With me, it will be quick.
很快
Quick as a flash.
我会让你看看中田没有的能力
I'll show you the finesse that Nakata lacks.
若头 -什么事?
Underboss. What?
谢谢先生
Thank you, sir.
我之前
I was...
什么?
What?
我…
I was...
想知道你会不会砍我的手指?
wondering if you could spare me the finger-chopping?
你在做什么梦?
Are you dreaming?
谁他妈的需要你的小指?
Who the fuck needs your pinky?
嗯?
Huh?
多谢
Thank you so much.
看好你的小手指
Take good care of your pinky.
是?
Yeah?
你父母给你的
Your parents gave it to you.
他们又问你要钱了吗?
They asked for money again?
从监狱里被放出来我们得去给花菱组送点钱
We must give a cash gift to a Hanabishi being released from prison.
我们是山王会为什么要这样?
We're Sanno. Why should we?
因为西野在保护我们
Because Nishino is our guardian.
我怀疑他是否会把钱上交给花菱组
I doubt he makes deposits to the Hanabishi account.
伙计们他们应该把木村的地盘还给我们
Man, they should give us back the Kimura turf.
它就在京东
It's in Tokyo.
嘿 我是组长 对我说话放尊重点
Hey, I'm the chairman! Don't speak as my equal.
抱歉先生我会注意的
Sorry, sir. I'll be careful.
蠢货!
Stupid!
对待来自木村组的吉岗先生要有礼貌
Courtesy of Mr. Yoshioka of the Kimura family.
木村组的吉岗?
Yoshioka of the Kimura?
在那边喝酒的那个人先生
That man drinking over there, sir.
嘿 朋友!
Hey, lost yakuza!
混蛋真想把他捏碎
Asshole. I'll crush him one clay.
该死l
Shit!
你准备好接替我的位置了吗?
Are you prepared to take over my position?
如果你准备好了就快点行动
Move fast if you are ready.
口恩?
Huh?
行动什么?
What should I do?
对西野做点事
Do something about Nishino.
杀了若头?
Kill the Underboss?
他和花田一起去找张道歉
He went with Hanada to apologize to Chang.
应该很容易让这事看起未像双方冲突的意外
It should be easy to make it look like a conflict.
当他晩上回来时干掉他
Strike him at night when he returns.
每个人都会认为是张干的
Everyone will accuse Chang.
明白吗中田?
You see, Nakata?
如果你想当组长你总得把障碍铲除
There are hurdles to overcome if you want to be a leader.
现在是你选择做或者死的时刻了
Your do-or-die moment.
但是花田必须得活着 因为我们还用的着他
But Hanada must live because we can use him.
到时候把张也杀了
While you're at it, eliminate Chang too.
他们将来只会妨碍我们
They will only get in our way.
不论谁赢了都将看上去是 花菱会和张氏集团的冲突
Whoever wins, it will look like a Nishino vs. Chang conflict.
动动你的脑子
Use your brain.
看看他们这些蠢脸l
Look at their stupid faces!
我们他妈的在这干嘛呀?
What the hell are we doing here?
我们还不属于花菱
We don't belong to the Hanabishi.
他们却把我们当做他们的佣人
They practically treat us like their servants.
无论怎样 这是事实 大友也参与其中了
Anyway, it appears Otomo had a part in this.
我希望花菱会和张氏集团都不会以停战告终
I hope the Hanabishi-Chang fight won't end in a truce.
然后我们就能重振山王会与他们抗争 就像以前一样
Then we can restore the Sanno to equal them as in the past.
你说的对
You're right.
大友
Otomo.
我觉得他还在济州島
I think he's still in Jeju.
我应该联系他么
Should I contact him?
这就是王先生关于香港计划的提议了
This is Mr. Wang's proposal on the Hong Kong project.
好的
Fine.
我可以继续么 会长大人?
Should I continue, Mr. Chairman?
好的
Fine.
张先生
Mr. Chang!
请看这个
Please look at this.
这个混账给您添了很大的麻烦
This asshole caused you a serious inconvenience.
我对此很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
这就是香港方面的价钱吗?
Is this the Hong Kong figure?
是的
Yes.
我们敬仰您的声誉
We're aware of your reputation.
关西地区也能听到您的名字
It spread to the Kansai region, too.
所以…
So...
作为花菱会的会长
on behalf of the Chairman of the Hanabishi...
我若头今天来亲自见您
I, Underboss Nishino, come to greet you in person today.
和韩国宾馆的差别不是太大
Not so different from Korean hotels.
好的 那么台湾呢?
Yes, and what about Taiwan?
您能原谅他么?
Will you forgive him?
我们在与这个开发商继续商讨并购的事项
We are proceeding acquisitions with this developer.
为了表示我们的兼憶
As a sign of our apology...
我带来了1亿的现金
I brought 100 million cash.
表明我们不会以低于80亿的价格卖出
Say we won't sell for less than 8 billion.
好的我会通知他们
Yes, I'll inform them.
这是英文版的
That's English.
感谢您远程前来
Thank you for traveling.
我们会接受3千万
We'll accept 30 million.
这只是你曾安排的数目
It's only the amount you had arranged.
您已做了一个友善的表率我们不是黑帮
You've made a friendly gesture. We're not yakuza.
我得请您离开了
I must ask you to leave.
我们不是在京都就餐吗?
Aren't we dining out in Kyoto?
他把我当成什么了?
Where the hell is he taking me?
那个站附近不是有很多馆子的么?
Aren't there many restaurants near the station?
我们走了多远了?
How far are we going?
中田告诉我跟着他的车
Mr. Nakata told me to follow his car.
我也不知道是哪儿
I don't know where.
中田和我曾在这条路上的一家饭馆吃饭
Mr. Nakata and I ate once in a Ryotei restaurant on this road.
现在是吃甜鱼最好的季节啊
It's the best season for sweetfish.
对我来说现在的淡水鱼尝起来才非常的有鱼味儿啊
Freshwater fish tastes too fishy for me.
我宁愿吃寿司
I'd rather have sushi.
为什么停在这样一个地方?
Why stop at a place like this?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们走错路了 得在这掉头
We took the wrong path. We'll turn around here.
快点 蠢货
Hurry up, moron!
我他妈的
What the fuck!
花田 -是我?
Hanada. Yes?
现在你站哪边?
Whose side are you on?
这是怎么了
What's going on?
他是谁?
Who is he?
当真?
Really?
你还不明白么?
You still don't understand?
听着
Listen.
野村组长
Chairman Nomura.
那个操蛋的
That motherfucker
想煽动中田
tried to instigate Nakata.
他还想让我死
He tried to rub me out.
把你和我一起打倒
And take you down with me.
不可能!
No way!
你知道我为他做了多少么?
You know how much I did for him?
你知道的对吧?
You know that, don't you?
别再局促不安了 你出不去的
Stop squirming. You're not getting out.
你跟哪边?
Whose side are you on?
在你出去前回答我
Answer before you get out.
我怎么会站在他那边呢
How could I possibly take his side
在这种情况下?
in this situation?
请你让我从车里出去!
Please let me get out the car!
好的你走吧
Fine, go.
告诉他们有人在张先生处袭击了我俩
Tell them someone attacked us both near Chang's office.
只有你活着出去了
Only you got out alive.
把这个告诉野村
Tell that to Nomura.
好的
Yes.
走吧开车
Go ahead and move the car.
好的 也把他扔到湖里
Fine. Dump him in the lake, too.
好的先生
Yes, sir.
什么一走吧
What? Let's go.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
若头
Underboss!
别忘了:你是唯一的幸存者!
Don't forget: You're the only survivor!
你为什么穿成那样?
Why are you dressed like that?
抱兼欠
I'm sorry.
我直接从水里出来的
I came directly from the site.
我跟手下借的这身行头
I borrowed these from one of my men.
西野怎么样?
What happened to Nishino?
我们的一个人被射杀
One of my men was shot to death.
我差点和西野先生淹死在湖里
I almost drowned in the lake with Mr. Nishino.
我设法从车里逃了出来
I managed to escape from the car on my own.
至于西野怎么样我还不清楚
I don't know what happened to Nishino.
他肯定死了
He must be dead.
对吧?
Right?
王八蛋 张
Motherfucker Chang!
我们要怎么处理张?
What do we do about Chang?
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
西野死了 我们不能轻易的让步
No backing down quietly after Nishino's death.
能做到吧花田?
Up to it, Hanada?
谁?
Who?
我么?
Me?
带上些人手
Get some guys together.
你能做到的
You can do it.
好的
Yes.
关于张你要打算怎么行动?
What are you doing about Chang?
我有个人一直在跟踪他
I got a man tailing him.
他常去他喜欢的那家咖啡店
He frequents his favorite coffee shop.
您的续杯
Your refill.
西野和张见面后就被袭击了
Nishino was attacked after the meeting with Mr. Chang.
花田的人正在路上
Hanada's men are on the way.
告诉他小心
Please tell him to watch out.
你打给崔了没?
Did you call Choi?
他的电话打不通 所以我打给了你
He was unreachable, so I called you.
知道了
Got it.
备好车
Get the car ready.
带上本台了吗 ?
Armed?
放回去 蠢货
Put it back, stupid.
我们再说一遍
Let's recap.
我们先射杀保標 对吧?
We shoot the bodyguards first. Alright?
对的
Yeah.
我们可以的
We can do this.
行动!
Let's move!
你还好么张先生?
Are you alright, Mr. Chang?
这有我来 你先走
I'll take care of this. Please go on ahead.
他们搞砸了 我们走
They screwed up. Let's go.
好的
Yeah.
那些废物永远都不能成事
Those punks were never going to succeed.
搞砸了?
A screw-up?
让张活着 杀了他的走狗 真是毫无意义
It's pointless to kill his henchmen and let Chang live!
花田只配和小混混一起干
Hanada only works with cheap punks.
你还指望他能把活给办了
You counted on him to do the job.
现在木村组也在行动了怎么办?
"The Kimura family is working on it." Now what?
现在是时候把那些杂碎收拾收拾了
It's time to get your shit together!
是
Yes.
事情进展的越发糟糕
Things are going from bad to worse.
他们不知道我们是幕后主使吧
They don't know we're behind this?
只有死人 不知道
Not the dead ones.
他们还没为结义金兰祝贺呢
They didn't drink to sworn brotherhood.
要是他们知道了 我不就扯蛋了
It's my ass if they find out!
你想当若头吗?
You want to be underboss?
振作点 解决它
Pull it together and resolve this!
好的
Yes.
张先生说他没事
Mr. Chang says he's alright.
他怎么可能没事
How could he be alright?
他们跟着他并杀了你的手下
They went after him and killed your henchmen.
如果您这么认为的话
If you see it that way.
我们难道让他们肆意妄为
We should let them do whatever?
到底谁是幕后黑手
Who the hell is behind this?
他们责怪我们对西野进行了攻击
They blame us for the attack on Nishino.
可能是花菱组里的某人做的
It might be someone inside the Hanabishi.
兄弟我可以和你一起走么?
Brother, can I go with you?
听着
Listen.
我不是你的组长
I'm not your boss
也不是你的兄弟
nor your brother.
你问错人了
You're asking the wrong person.
如果我问李先生 他会拒绝
If I ask Mr. Lee, he'll say no.
他也拒绝我了
He already told me no.
那现在呢?
What now?
你要怎么办?
What would you do?
看花菱组怎么做吧
Go after the Hanabishi.
你会死的
You'll die.
死就死吧
So be it.
张氏是韩国政治工业的代理人和首脑
Chang is the fixer and mastermind of Korean politics and industry.
我们还没有找出是哪个人攻击了他
We have yet to identify the punks who attacked him.
我只知道和花菱组有关
We only know they are connected to the Hanabishi.
片岗警员已经在行动了
Osaka Police is on it.
这是针对花田的复仇计划
It's either vengeance against Hanada
或是对西野的反击报复但他仍处于失踪
or retaliation for Nishino, but he's still missing.
韩国代理人对上花菱组
Korean fixer vs. Hanabishi.
我们先去张那儿吧
First we go to Chang.
你最好小心
You'd better watch out.
他非常有影响力一个小失误都可能满盘皆输
He's influential. One wrong move could lead to a diplomatic issue.
我曾和片岗先生去过那
I went there once with Mr. Kataoka,
当他从监狱被释放的时候我们跟踪着大友
when we tailed Otomo after his release from prison.
我们是都市警察我们有些问题问你
We're from the Metropolitan Police. We have some questions for you.
这是让我们走进去吗 ?
Is he telling us to walk?
傲慢的狗屎
Pompous ass!
花菱组发生了什么?
Something happen with the Hanabishi?
我已经告诉另一个警官了
I already told another officer:
我们什么都不知道
We know nothing.
所以当你在咖啡店被袭击的时候你毫不知情 ?
So no clue why you were attacked in the coffee house?
在佐野和花菱组的冲突的那段时间我有调査一些案子
I worked on some cases during the Sanno-Hanabishi conflict.
有个叫大友的瘪三和你联系了
There was a yakuza named Otomo who was associated with you.
我觉得冲突之后 他就在济州島定居
I think he settled in Jeju after the conflict.
他和这个事情有什么联系呢?
What's his connection to this?
他专程去了一趟花菱组
He paid a visit to the Hanabishi.
他最终还是被放逐了
He was eventually banished.
你会承认这件事和这个案子有些许关联么?张先生?
Would you admit it's somehow related to this case, Mr. Chang?
如今 日本警察真没有礼貌
These days, Japanese police have no manners.
抱歉
Sorry.
张先生很忙我必须请您高开了
Mr. Chang is busy. I must ask you to leave.
来吧 咱们走
Come on, let's go.
别管了他们会开始互相屠杀
Leave it. They'll start killing each other.
但是我们不能毫无头结地空手而归
But we can't leave empty-handed without a clue.
这就是那个大友么?
Isn't that Otomo?
就是他
It's him.
他打算去哪?
What's he up to?
我们拘留他吧
Let's detain him.
你怎么拿到你的护照的?
How did you get your passport?
老枪我安排的
Gun arranged it for me.
李先生
Mr. Lee.
怎么?
Yes?
请不要告诉张先生
Please keep it secret from Mr. Chang.
关于老枪的事也不要说
About Gun too.
好的
Yes.
请靠边停车
Pull over your vehicle.
车牌号 银色奔驰
Plate number S300A5573. Silver Mercedes.
他们已经在跟踪我们了
They're tailing me already.
我知道你刚到 但是请和我们去一个地方
I know you just landed, but take a ride to the station with us.
让开
Move over.
组长
Mr. Chairman!
混蛋
Assholes!
这不防弹
It's not bulletproof!
我可能被杀了
I could have been shot!
快收拾干净
Clean up this mess now!
好的先生!
Yes, sir!
快点
Move it!
别说这方言 我讨厌关西口音
Don't use that dialect. I hate the Kansai accent!
你滚
You move it!
滚开别挡我道
Out of my way!
他是哪个组的?
Which family is he from?
有人知道么?
Anybody know?
抱歉
Excuse me.
中田!花田
Nakata! Hanada!
哦 你肯定就河野了
Oh, you must be Kono.
很荣幸重冬于見到了你
Honored to finally meet you.
今天出狱了么?
Get out of prison today?
对不起我不能像前组长对你那么好客
Sorry I can't be as hospitable to you as the former boss.
先忍着吧
Bear with me.
我毫不介意
I don't mind at all.
你看上去不错
You're looking well.
尽管 几分钟前我差点被杀
Although, I was almost killed a few minutes ago!
调动你的人和在东京 村组的所有人
Mobilize all your men and the Kimura family in Tokyo.
推毁张氏
Destroy Chang now.
我已经在他们必除名单上了
I'm already on their hit list.
等一下
Hold on a second.
就是花田引起了这场冲突
It was Hanada who caused this conflict.
我们让现场看起来像西野和张
We made it look like Nishino vs. Chang.
我告诉你那只是个托辞
And I told you it was a pretext
是为了让你完美的策划 然后我就推举你为接班人
for you to mastermind perfectly, then I'd make you my successor.
现在我在暗杀名単上
Now I'm on their hit list.
对警察和张来说 你显然就是幕后人物
To both the police and Chang, you're obviously behind this.
赶快解决好不然我们会成为所有人的笑柄
Fix this or we'll be ridiculed by everyone.
山王会
SANNO ENTERPRISES
白山先生在吗 -在的
Is Mr. Shiroyama here? He's inside.
打流了
Excuse me.
现在不行
Not now.
好的先生
Yes, sir.
这确实是花菱和张之间的冲突
This is really a conflict between the Hanabishi and Chang.
笨蛋
Idiot!
他们杀了西野 他是你的头儿
They murdered brother Nishino, who was your guardian.
你应该第一个站出来杀张
You should be first in line to attack Chang.
给我闭嘴否则我就废了山王会
Cut your bullshit or I'll destroy the Sanno.
好笑吗
What's so funny?
中田
Nakata!
闭嘴
Shut your mouth.
至少试一下
At least try!
什么
What?
你只是个副手 搞得像你是我们的头目一样
You're just a deputy acting like our guardian.
或者你觉得你已经接管整个组了
Or you think you already took over the family?
嗯
Huh?
你怎么
What's with you?
西野走的那一刻起
The minute Mr. Nishino was gone,
你的态度完全变了
you had a complete change of attitude.
笨蛋
Stupid ass.
让开
Out of my way!
别站在这里挡路
Don't just stand there!
进来
Coming in!
欺负弱小可不体面
It's not nice to bully the weak.
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
不要像見到鬼一样看着我
Don't look at me like I'm a fucking ghost.
白痴
Shitheads.
花菱组正面临着分月崩 瓦解的危机
The Hanabishi is in danger of disintegration.
必要时 我们应该和平相处
We must work together amicably when necessary.
没人教过你吗
No one ever taught you that?
舍弟
You punks!
张先生提醒说拘留大友太久
Mr. Chang warns that detaining Otomo longer
会让警局陷入不可逆转的局势
might put the police into an overwhelming situation.
我没有意识到这个麻烦
I wasn't aware of this inconvenience.
我会妥善安排的
I will settle it quietly.
我只是建议
I advise that.
我受够这种形式了 已经两天了
I've had enough of this. It's been two days.
山王会的加藤若头背叛了你 木村接管了那个组
Boss Kato of the Sanno betrayed you. Kimura got his family.
片岗利用你击垮山王
Kataoka used you to break up the Sanno.
你干掉了他们三个人
You got rid of three of them!
我怎么知道
Fuck if I know!
我会让你不能再开口
I'll make sure you never talk again.
快点混蛋
Do it, motherfucker!
你们两个哑了吗
You two are total dumbasses.
片岗没有告诉你们吗
Didn't Kataoka tell you anything?
什么
What?
怎么了
What is it?
上面说不要问太多
The higher-ups said not to dig deeper.
张可能施压了 放了大友
Chang probably pressured to release Otomo.
你可以走了
You can go.
非常感谢
Thanks so much.
总是发号施令现在怎么样
After all that bossing around, now what?
你老大下令了 结束了
An order from your boss and it's over.
我自由了
I'm free to go!
废物
Punk!
他是重要证人
He's a material witness.
你怎么让他走了那个下流
How can you let him go? That intimidating bastard!
我们应该拘留他10天或20天
We should detain him for another 10 or 20 days!
不管张说什么警局为什么轻易听他的
Whatever Chang says, why must the police obey him so easily?
放松 -狗屁
Relax. Bullshit!
警局最黑暗
The police are the dirtiest!
看看谁在说话
Look who's talking!
冷静 –闭嘴
Calm down! Shut up!
本字幕首发于字幕库 www.zimuku.cn
一切还好吗
Everything alright?
你的车在这里
Your car is here.
张先生叫你接我吗
Mr. Chang told you to pick me up?
是的
Yes.
李先生
Mr. Lee,
我要去一个地方
I have to go somewhere.
你能一个人回去吗
Can you drive back alone?
你有什么事吗
Are you up to something?
你让佐野和其他人跟你一起
You asked Ichikawa and others to join you.
不需要
I did no such thing.
张先生不想惹麻烦
Mr. Chang doesn't want any more trouble.
把佐野妥妥的送回韩国去
Kindly take Ichikawa back to Korea.
张先生要求的
Mr. Chang's request.
请告诉他我回济州島了
Please tell him I went back to Jeju.
我不会给他添麻烦
I will cause him no trouble.
那里无疑是个遥远的地方 -是啊
It had to be a remote place. Yeah.
他们监视着我
They have eyes on me.
这是老本台
This is Gun.
他准备了护照那些东西
He arranged passports and everything.
对不起 护照随便起的名字
Sorry about the random passport names.
五郎 山野这个名字不错
I'm fine with Goro Yamada.
我拿了武器
I loaded the firearms in the back.
随你挑 只是有些旧了点
Take your pick, although some are old.
那么现在
So, what now?
第一件事
First thing...
打倒东京的花菱会
we take down the Hanabishi in Tokyo.
老大 我们在这里喝酒安全吗
Boss, are we safe drinking in this kind of place?
请原谅
Can you excuse us?
进来吧姑娘们
Come on, girls.
你什么意思
What do you mean by that?
在我的地盘上喝酒有什么问题
What's wrong with drinking on my turf?
对吗
Right?
我的想法对吗
My thoughts exactly.
关西的家伙们选择跟张抄架
The Kansai guys chose to quarrel with Chang.
我们东京的人要和睦相处
We in Tokyo should get along.
对
True!
袭击花田的事
About the attack on Hanada...
没人怀疑我们不用担心
No one suspects our involvement yet, so stop worrying.
我安排吉岗跟我们接头告诉你位置
I arranged Yoshioka to meet us and told you where he is.
别以为付出了代价一切就结束了
Don't think it's over, simply because you paid.
山崎在哪
Where's Yamazaki?
他在楼上 我能帮你吗
He's upstairs. Can I help?
警察
Police.
老板
Boss?
什么
What?
警察来了
The police are here.
快走
Leave us.
好
Okay.
探长 我宁愿你没有出现在这里
Detective, I rather you not show up here.
原谅我
Bear with me.
我有些关于木村的问题
I have some questions about the late Kimura.
你是山王会会长加藤的副手
You were an aide of Kato, the former Sanno chairman.
你怀疑我是嫌疑犯
Are you implying I'm a suspect?
饶了我吧
Give me a break.
片図没有给你本台吗 没让你干掉木村?
Didn't Kataoka give you guns and tell you to make a raid on Kimura?
木村组这样的被杀 我根本不在乎
I don't give a damn if a yakuza like Kimura was killed.
另外
Besides,
你还没達捕杀加藤的凶手
you haven't arrested the perp that killed Kato.
我知道他在哪里就見鬼了
Damned if I know where he's at.
茂田
Shigeta speaking.
夜总会枪战
Nightclub shootout?
那是大友吗
Is it Otomo?
仔细搜査
Canvassing the area.
我要回去了
I'm heading back.
探长
Detective?
大友回日本了吗
Is Otomo back in Japan?
管好自己的事回头再聊
Mind your own business. We'll talk later.
第二小组人手不足
The 2nd Division is short-handed.
真的
Really?
让他低调点
Tell him to lay low for a while.
现在起所有跟张联系的事情都要经过我
All contact with Chang must go through me from now on.
好的先生
Yes, sir.
他说什么高张远点
What did he say? To stay away from Chang?
差不多吧
Something like that.
没关系让我逮捕大友
It doesn't matter. Let's arrest Otomo on this.
应该的茂田
We should, Shigeta.
因为现在你被分配到第二组
For now, you're transferred to the 2nd Division.
为什么我被排除在外
Why am I off the case?
上面说的
The order came from above.
让大友杀了吉岗是最好的
Letting Otomo kill Yoshioka was perfect.
监控摄像头关了
Surveillance cameras off.
我们现在是官方目击证人
We are now officially victims who happened to be there.
他们最终会判大友罪名成立
They will eventually conclude Otomo did it.
我想也是但是
I think so, but...
木村组怎么办
what happens to the Kimura family?
我希望花菱组撤退 回到自己的地盘
I wish the Hanabishi would withdraw and return the turf.
这对我们有利
That wouldn't be in our favor.
另外我们要回地盘合适吗
Besides, is the timing right for us to get it back?
他们会怀疑我们的好好想想
They will suspect us. Think harder!
花菱会
It's the Hanabishi.
发生什么了
Hello. Has something happened?
他总是拍花菱的马屁
He's always sucking up to the Hanabishi!
像大友一样行动
Take action like Otomo!
傻瓜
Stupid asshole!
我想是不是可以讨论一下怎么处置大友
I was wondering if we could discuss what to do with Otomo.
我明白
I see.
给我电话如果你发现什么
Give me a call if you find anything.
好
Yeah.
好像是大友干的
It seems Otomo did it.
我要告诉张
I'll call Chang.
花菱的中田来电话
A phone call from Mr. Nakata of the Hanabishi.
中田
Nakata?
告诉他秘书不方便接听
Tell him the secretary is unavailable to take messages.
好的明白
Yes, understood.
他的秘书不方便
His secretary is unavailable.
请晩些打来
Please call back later.
混蛋中田
That bastard Nakata.
他只会打电话抱怨
He only made calls and complained.
没用的东西
A useless prick!
这个大友是个什么鬼
Who the hell is this Otomo anyway?
他就是个无名小辈除掉他
He's just a punk. Get rid of him.
我已经安排好了
I've arranged that.
看好社团 废物
Take care of business. Incompetent!
好的
Yes.
尹先生派我们来的
Mr. Yoon sent us.
非常感谢
Thanks so much.
我们准备好了听后吩咐
We are ready and at your service.
大友先生
And Mr. Otomo?
在车里
In the car.
晩上好
Good evening.
进来
Get in.
问问尹夫人在做什么
Ask him how Mrs. Yoon is doing.
好
Yes.
尹夫人怎么样
How is Mrs. Yoon?
她很好
She's fine.
她向大友先生问好
She sends her regards to Mr. Otomo.
他说她很好
He said she's fine.
带她问好
She sends her regards.
杀了他们 市川
Kill them, Ichikawa!
我打中了我们自己人
I shot my own man.
他们从哪来的
Where did they come from?
对不起
Sorry.
他说尹先生派他们来帮我们的
He said Mr. Yoon sent them to help us.
一定是花菱
It must be the Hanabishi.
他们准备了这些
They even prepared these.
只有我们两个人了
Only two of us left.
你拿了些垃圾武器
You got some mean weapons!
不要惊慌
No surprise.
被伏击了吗
Got attacked?
我听说了
So I've heard.
放下武器
Put down your weapons.
我们没有武器
We're unarmed.
我们谈谈吧
Let's have a chat.
你命令他们这么做
You ordered them to do it?
为什么你不做
Why would we do that?
大友
Hey, Otomo!
是混蛋野村
It was that bastard Nomura.
好久不見
Long time no see.
我以为你已经死了
I thought you were dead.
不如你
No more than you.
野村差点把我杀了
Nomura almost got me killed.
但是我们有些人就是没有那么容易死
But some of us don't die easily.
这才刚刚开始
It all started
因为花田的愚蠢行动
with Hanada's stupid actions.
尊重点
Show some fucking respect!
我不知道到你是大友先生
I didn't realize you were Mr. Otomo.
很抱歉在济州島做了那样的事情
I apologize for my behavior in Jeju.
请原谅我
Please forgive me.
如果你告诉我你是谁结果就会不一样
Things would have been different if you had told me who you were.
你老板和我在花田的事情上达成了协议
Your boss and I reached an agreement concerning Hanada.
但野村又去插手别人的事情
But Nomura put his nose in other people's business again.
没有什么可以做了
There's nothing left to do.
他必须退休了
He must retire!
你老板更喜欢这样对吗
Your boss prefers that. Doesn't he?
你能前嫌尽释吗
Can you put all that behind us?
也许能助我们一臂之力
Maybe give us a helping hand?
我们为河野干部考备了一场欢迎会
We're throwing a welcome home party for an executive named Kono.
那混蛋野村应该在那
That bastard Nomura will be there.
我想你
I want you...
把他处理了
to dispose of him.
我要把
I will give you
木村组交给你 只要你圆满完成任务
the Kimura family if you can pull it off.
我不要
I don't want it.
所以你不想去
So you won't go?
不
No.
这派对为他准备的
The party's for him,
但是他的手下杀了人
but his soldier did the killing.
他在牢里被关了五年
He served five years.
我为什么要给他一大笔钱?
Why should I give him exorbitant gift money?
是我提拔他做干部的
I promoted him to executive.
好 我会通知他们
Fine. I'll inform them.
欢迎回来河野先生
Welcome Home, Mr. Naoki Kono.
这边请 河野!
Way to go, Kono!
事情怎么样了? -野村先生不来了
What's going on? Mr. Nomura is not coming.
没来?
No?
那个贪婪的混蛋!
Typical of that greedy bastard!
这样更好
All the better.
在他不在的时候我要宣布一两件事
In his absence, I'll announce a thing or two
然后炫耀下枪支
and show off some guns.
所有人都会到我这边来
Everyone will jump to my side.
是
Yes.
还有 大友会支持我的 给他发个信息
By the way, Otomo will have my back. Send him a message.
告诉他我们取消了暗杀野村的计划
Tell him we call off the plan to shoot Nomura.
之前我检査的时候发现他不在
He wasn't there the last time I checked.
什么?
What?
他真没用
He's useless.
感谢大家来参加这个聚会
Thank you for such a great party.
我感到很荣幸
I am greatly humbled to be in the presence
能有这么多我的上级来参加
of so many of my superiors.
这是对我的盛誉
The honor is more than I deserve.
野村组长 西野若头
Chairman Nomura, Underboss Nishino,
还有若头輔佐们
and ranking deputy underbosses,
我不会辜负你们对我的信任
I shall honor your confidence in me.
我会为花菱组的荣誉而奋斗
I am dedicated to Hanabishi prosperity...
若头!
Underboss!
河野
Kono.
抱歉 扫兴了
Sorry to crash your party.
大家听着
Listen up.
几天前
A few days ago,
我你们的西野若头
I, Underboss Nishino,
差点被
was nearly killed
野村组长干掉
by Chairman Nomura.
如果不是中田提前告诉我
If Nakata had not told me beforehand,
我这个人早就死了
I would have been wiped from existence.
明白了吗?
See?
你们得知道
You should know,
在你们为了组里在拼命工作时
you who work your asses off to serve the family...
野村他根本就不在乎你们
Nomura doesn't care shit about you.
现在我只想说
All this to now say,
我要断绝对他的忠诚关系
I must sever my loyal ties to him.
我要问你们
I ask you this:
是支持野村
Side with Nomura
还是支持我
or side with me.
现在就选
Choose now.
晩上好
Good evening.
请签到
Sign in, please.
大友!
Otomo!
谁让你开枪的?
Who told you to shoot?
疯子!你真是疯了
Mad motherfucker! You're out of your fucking mind.
疯子l
Mad motherfucker!
你确定野村就在家里?
Are you sure Nomura is at home?
是的我检査过了
Yes. I had them check.
大友那个恶魔
That fiend Otomo
把所有能动的活人 都打死了
shot everything that moved.
他可能把整个花菱组灭口了
He might have killed every Hanabishi.
不管怎么样 我都要把大友碎尸万段
I would have crushed Otomo in any other situation.
别想了
Forget it.
那个混蛋野村
That fucker Nomura,
大友可以抓住他的!
Otomo can have him!
他把所有人都灭口了?
He killed all of them?
中田 你被组织除名了
Nakata, you're banished.
如果所有人都死了 我们会怎么样?
What would happen to us if all our guys got killed?
我会让你知道的
I'll tell you.
这是你的计划
It was your plan.
你被组织除名了
You're banished.
是你吗?
Is that you?
西野你还活着!
Nishino, you're still alive!
还活着?这个话不听
Still? That's not nice.
你和中田两个人在密谋把我给赶走
You were plotting with Nakata to rub me out.
中田好心地告诉了我所有事情
Nice guy Mr. Nakata kindly informed me of everything.
不要这样对你的义父说话
That's no way to speak to your sworn father.
去你的义父!
Screw your father-son bullshit!
中田!
Nakata!
你怎么敢背叛你的老大?
How dare you betray your boss?
你觉得谁更重要?义父还是兄弟?
Who's more important? Sworn father or brother?
野村…
Nomura...
我们从来没觉得
We never ever thought of you
你是个黑帮或者是义父
as a yakuza nor a father.
你身上没有纹身
You don't have tattoos.
你也没坐过牢
You've never been to prison.
你就是个外行!
You're a fucking amateur!
一个外行天天自称是花菱组组长
A fucking amateur who calls himself chairman of the Hanabishi.
别骗我们了!
You can't fool us!
森島 动手
Morishima, do something about him.
我为什么要在意?
Why should I care?
没了小弟你就是个退休 的办公室职员
You're just a retired office worker without your henchmen.
本字幕首发于字幕库 www.zimuku.cn
你也这样?
You too?
你也要背叛我?
You're betraying me?
背叛这个词太严重了
Betray is too strong a word.
听着好像我以前一直是你的人
It gives the impression that I was on your side.
原谅我组长
Forgive me, Chairman.
你们会为此后悔的
You'll all regret this.
嘿
Hey,
野村
Nomura.
如果你是个真正的黑道人
If you're a real yakuza,
被子弹打穿就是你的结局
then pumping you with bullets is your end.
我可以告诉你 黑帮到底有多可怕
I can show you how gruesome yakuza really are.
把他带出去 -是!
Take him out. Yes!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
把你的手拿开!
Take your hands off me!
我是你的组长!
I'm your Chairman!
出去!
Get out!
住手l
Stop it!
你是谁?
Who are you?
我说话算话
Just as I promised.
大友你来干什么?
Otomo, what are you doing?
我是花菱组的组长
I'm Chairman of the Hanabishi.
你没这个能力胜任
You don't have what it takes.
我带你去
I'm going to take you
挖点东西
on a little excavation.
那边有人吗?
Anybody out there?
救命!有人被困住了!
Help! A man's stuck down here!
救命!
Help!
噢 该死!
Oh, shit!
不 不 我在这
No, no. I'm here.
我被困在这儿了
I'm stuck down here.
就差那么一点儿
That was fucking close!
你差点杀了我
You could have killed me.
不…
No...
下面这里!
Down here!
我们跟花菱组和解了
We have settled with the Hanabishi.
那怎么替河野报仇?
How do we avenge Ko's death?
我有主意
I have some ideas.
好
Good.
事情一直有些复杂
There have been some complications.
野村已经死了
Mr. Nomura has passed on.
我们这些活下来的
We, survivors,
必须齐心协力重建组织
must work hard to restore the family.
今天
As of today,
花菱组換了新组长
the Hanabishi is under new administration.
我任命自己成为你们新的组长
I am appointing myself as your new Chairman.
中田是你们的若头
Nakata is your underboss.
花田是若头輔佐
Hanada is a deputy underboss.
我希望新的管理者能够齐心协力重现组织的繁荣
I expect the new administration to commit to achieving prosperity.
是的组长!
Yes, sir!
好
Fine.
先生
Sir.
等一下
One moment.
谢谢
Thanks.
是什么?
Yes. What is it?
真的吗?怎么样了?
Really? How was it?
太过分!
Too much!
我的想法?
My answer?
当然是的
Of course, yes!
再見
Bye.
花田 -是
Hanada. Yes?
你怎么看起来那么累?又出去找女人了?
Why are you so wired? Going out for women again?
是有点累
Sort of.
西野先生和中田先生给我的庆祝活动安排了些站娘
Mr. Nishino and Mr. Nakata arranged some girls for my celebration.
你连个靠谱的亲信都没有
You don't even have proper henchmen.
他们只在你钱给的多的时候才口所从你
They only treat you nicely because you pay a lot.
想一起来吗 兄弟?
Want to come along, brother?
我可不赞成你这个曲解的观点
I don't approve of your perversions.
服从官僚是你在警察队伍中取得成功的唯一途径
Obeying bureaucracy is the only way to get ahead on the police force.
繁田 别这么愤青好吧
Shigeta, don't be so cynical.
那你给我点新鲜的
Give me an update.
我被一个公开案子排除在外了
I was thrown off an open case.
野村计划灭口西野 然后提拔中田顶替他
Nomura plotted to kill Nishino and to promote Nakata in his place.
西野和中田秘密联手欺骗了野村
Nishino and Nakata corresponded secretly to deceive Nomura.
官方的报道把这件事归咎于另一个组织
The official story blames another family.
没人了解真相
No one knows the real truth.
真的?
Really?
恭喜晋升!
Congratulations on your promotion.
少讽刺了
No need for sarcasm.
别客气 我请客
Don't bother. It's my treat.
辞职信
Letter of Resignation.
西野先生通知我了
Mr. Nishino informed me.
入口在那边
The entrance is that way.
好
Fine.
你来了
But you're coming.
坐
Sit down.
你在那干吗?
What are you doing here?
长得不错!
Good look!
你俩可以走了
You two can go.
一会儿你嘴里会冒出烟花的
Your mouth will see fireworks.
大友!
Otomo!
你们想说什么?
What do you want to talk about?
我听说花田被杀了
I heard Hanada was attacked.
这儿可能不安全
It may not be safe here.
是的
Right.
一点都不安全
Not safe at all.
有人吗?
Hello?
大友突袭了我们的办公室
Otomo made a raid on our office.
让我们单独呆会
Give us a moment alone.
好的
Excuse me.
大友对于我们的要求出乎意料地非常合作
Otomo was unexpectedly cooperative about our requests.
我也没料到他会把花田灭口
I didn't expect him to eliminate Hanada.
不过也是理所当然
But of course.
毕竟花田是问题的福根
After all, Hanada was the source of the problem.
对于自己该做的事 大友真的是一丝不苟
Otomo is quite meticulous when it comes to sense of duty.
只要我们不动张
As long as we don't touch Chang,
他会按照我们说的做
he'll do what we ask.
多谢了他
Thanks to him,
我们才能控制得了花田的地盘和收入
we got control of Hanada's turf and revenue.
你现在的手段真是越来越厉害
Your methods are increasingly more intricate.
当他让整个聚会陷入混乱时 我整个人都紧张了
My blood froze when he went haywire at the party.
你们打算对大友做什么?
What do you plan to do about Otomo?
大友!
Otomo!
他给花菱组造成了毁灭性的打击
He wreaked havoc on the Hanabishi.
那个老派的流氓的确是对我们很有帮助
That old-fashioned gangster definitely served us well.
我们要让他走到痛苦的尽头
We go for him to the bitter end.
你要做什么?
What will you do?
张手下的那个李说他来做这件事
That guy Lee who works for Chang said he would take on the task.
我们对花田被谋杀非常气愤
We are annoyed at Hanada's murder.
他们得给个说法
We want them to settle the score.
我就是这么告诉李的
That's what we tell Lee.
西野打电话和我说
Nishino called to inform me.
花田被杀了
Hanada has been killed.
我解释说我们并没有参与这件事
I explained we had no part in it.
告诉大友
Tell Otomo
如果他是为了我 那他做的已经够多了
if he did it for me, then he's done enough.
谢谢你
Thank you.
如果你要来济州島告诉我
Let me know if you come to Jeju.
我带你转转
I'll take you around.
我们一块芸芸泡菜锅
We'll try that kimchi stew.
你什么时候回去?
When will you be back?
我还有事没做完
I still have something to do.
做事别太鲁莽
Don't be too reckless.
我该走了
I should get going.
我们没想给日本警察惹麻烦
We have no intention of making trouble for the Japanese police.
谢谢
Thank you.
大友离开了吗?
Did Otomo leave?
是的一分钟前市川打电话说了
Yes. Ichikawa called a minute ago.
告诉他…
Tell him...
我想让大友给我打个电话
I want Otomo to call me.
好我一会儿去做
Yes, I'll do that.
这个汽车站?
This auto shop?
杀了木村的那两个人就在这工作
The two guys who killed Kimura work here.
最后一件事办完后你应该离开这
You should leave after this last job.
大友!
Otomo!
所以就是它了
So, this is it.
大友先生
Mr. Otomo,
原谅我
forgive me.
我不能让你再给张先生惹麻烦了
I can't allow you to make anymore trouble for Mr. Chang.
没必要李先生
No need, Mr. Lee.
我可以自己来
I can take care of myself.
代我向张先生问好
My regards to Mr. Chang.
大友先生死了
Mr. Otomo is dead.
他真死了?
He is?
他让我给你问好
He told me to give you his regards.
有东西上钩了
Somethings pulling.
我抓住了吗?
Did I catch one?
抓圧了兄弟!我们一会儿拿它炖泡菜锅
Got it, brother! We'll have that kimchi stew.
看那 兄弟
Look at that, brother.